{
    "id": "8d61700a2ad34643a0c20645be482c64",
    "title": "Determiners Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "There weren't ................................ students in the class.",
            "description": "We use many before plural nouns and much before uncountable nouns.",
            "answers": [
                "few",
                "little",
                "much",
                "many"
            ],
            "correct": 3,
            "id": "18f352dedc0141aab848abe29e1937a6"
        },
        {
            "question": "He doesn't have ................................. patience.",
            "description": "We use much before an uncountable noun.",
            "answers": [
                "much",
                "many",
                "little",
                "a lot"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "5c704b13a198489682afa48ab059e4cd"
        },
        {
            "question": "We haven't got ............................. time to prepare for the test.",
            "description": "We use much before uncountable nouns. ",
            "answers": [
                "much",
                "many",
                "little"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "e6f3d90a97614311802ab343104d5b76"
        },
        {
            "question": "I like your parents ............................",
            "description": "Much is not normally used with like and dislike in affirmative clauses.",
            "answers": [
                "much",
                "a lot",
                "a lot of"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "6d57ff35426f4a08aa76a5a823d9a0b6"
        },
        {
            "question": "I managed to solve the puzzle with .............................. difficulty.",
            "description": "We use little before uncountable nouns. ",
            "answers": [
                "little",
                "few",
                "many",
                "lesser"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "95f73ac306df4a24b85f777a8e27600a"
        },
        {
            "question": "I got ............................. apples than her.",
            "description": "Fewer is the comparative form of few. We use it before a plural noun.",
            "answers": [
                "few",
                "fewer",
                "less",
                "lesser"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "c5953ce9d1e44389b4a9b823e8bcf6bb"
        },
        {
            "question": "I earn ................................. than my sister.",
            "description": "In this context, less is the comparative form of little. ",
            "answers": [
                "fewer",
                "less",
                "lesser"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "e7a0b5dafc7f484288e4efb4a40c6bd6"
        },
        {
            "question": "We experienced far .................................. problems than we were expecting.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "few",
                "fewer",
                "less"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "0d814102ce3044ab95381d2008624f69"
        },
        {
            "question": "The company does not make ............................... money these days.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "many",
                "much",
                "a lot"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "f64d84a150c948cd8eacb63ab2aa0883"
        },
        {
            "question": "............................. want a new system.",
            "description": "Many is not normally used alone to mean 'many people'.",
            "answers": [
                "Many",
                "Many people",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "a5716aa718e7457cb7b18581a5d31cd2"
        },
        {
            "question": "She is extremely close to ................................. friends she has.",
            "description": "The few means not many but all that you have. ",
            "answers": [
                "few",
                "a few",
                "the few"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "2b7e9b62466d46a28e3f34fe3876b46e"
        },
        {
            "question": "I .............................. enjoyed my stay with your family.",
            "description": "Much can be an adverb.",
            "answers": [
                "much",
                "a lot",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "74c415430134455ead4c2384f0950b52"
        }
    ]
}